<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DialogueData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <fileName>MiCherie</fileName>
  <allDialogues>
   <Snippet>
      <keyword>Hello</keyword>
      <section>
        <body>Hello There!
	  
My name is Mi Cherie, knight errant, dancer and monster hunter extraordinaire. Currently here in Ponyville on duty.</body>
        <local>
          <string>Knight</string>
		  <string>Dancer</string>
        </local>
        <global />
      </section>
    </Snippet>
	    <Snippet>
      <keyword>Knight</keyword>
      <section>
        <body>Indeed, knight errant. Well, maybe not that errant, but it sounds more romantic that way. I am in fact a member of the royal guard, Captain Cherie at your service.
	  
But it is not wholly incorrect, my position have me traveling around a lot, I take initiative to start my own investigations and keep myself useful for Equestria and the Princesses. Tho currently I am commissioned with a problem here in Ponyville.</body>
        <local>
          <string>Problem</string>
        </local>
        <global />
      </section>
    </Snippet>
	    <Snippet>
      <keyword>Dancer</keyword>
      <section>
        <body>Yes, a Dancer. I earned my cutemark way back in Canterlot on the dance floor. Of course I joined the dance club in Canterlot high and I did really well. I would have made it a dancer like most of my peers but it did not stay entirely right with me. I had my true calling elsewhere so to say. A cutiemark is just a talent after all, the weapon, not the warrior or her quest.
	  
One thing led to another and I joined the royal guard. Now you might think that is an odd place for a dancer, but really, a tussle is not all that different from a dance. The clash of swords is my rhythm and the enemy is my dance partner, fighting is an art after-all, and as a dancer, my talent is performing art with my body in motion.</body>
        <local />
        <global />
      </section>
    </Snippet>
	    <Snippet>
      <keyword>Problem</keyword>
      <section>
        <body>I don't know what yet. But the monster activity in the Everfree Forest is increasing. At the moment my hoofs are tied, I have to stay close to Ponyville and react in case of a monster attack. I'm hoping I could get some reinforcement soon enough so I could actually head out there and do some investigation.
	  
Say, I have ran into many other thrill seekers and explorers in my career and you have that eagerness to explore written all over your face. I heard that there is a Zebra living in there with the name of Zecora, surely somebody who actually live in the thick of it would have some more insight into the situation. Now I am not asking you to do my work for me, but if you would decide to explore the forest and happen upon her, would you be so kind as to ask her about the situation on my behalf.</body>
        <local />
        <global>
		 <string>Zecora</string>
		</global>
      </section>
    </Snippet>
  </allDialogues>
</DialogueData>